https://quintemidwives.ca/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
BEFORE USING OUR SITES, PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.
This Privacy Policy is applicable to Quinte Midwives (“Company”) and sets out our policy on the gathering and use of information on this site. The Company is committed to providing safe websites for visitors of all ages and has implemented this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The Company complies with Canadian Federal and Provincial privacy laws and regulations including the Personal Information and Electronic Documents Act.
There may be links from our site to other web sites; note that this Privacy Policy applies only to our site and not to web sites of other companies or organizations to which our site may be linked. You must check on any linked sites for the privacy policy that applies to that site and/or make any necessary inquiries in respect of that privacy policy with the operator of the linked site. These links to third party websites are provided as a convenience and are for informational purposes only. The Company does not endorse, and is not responsible for, these linked websites.
Although you are not required to register to access our site, you may be asked to provide us with personal information when you visit certain sections of our site. Your use of our site signifies your acknowledgement and consent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not continue to use our site. Your continued use of the site signifies your acceptance of these terms and any changes in effect at the time of use.
Updated: January 1, 2019
Search for:
Recent Posts
Hello world!
© Copyright Quinte Midwives. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy.
